
TRENDS OBSERVED FROM PYBER PLOTS:

1) The average fare per city is higher in suburban areas as opposed to rural and urban areas. This trend is clear by looking at the bubble plot and the pie plot for total fare of each city type. The second in the list is suburban and then rural.

2) The bubble plot also depicts that the number of rides per city are much higher than the rural and urban areas. This trend is also very clear in the pie plot of percent rides per city type.

3)The number of drivers in the urban areas are much higher than the other two city types. This trend is pretty clear looking at the lat pie chart depicting the number of drivers per city type. The second one below that is the number of drivers in suburban areas and the rural areas have significantly lower number of drivers.